另一个重要的monadic图像处理操作是伽马校正，我要去了
Another important monadic image processing operation is gamma correction, and I am going
现在谈谈伽玛的问题。
to talk now about the problem of gamma.
早在电视的早期，选择的显示装置就是阴极射线
Back in the early days of television, the display device of choice was the cathode ray
管和阴极管是非常非线性的装置。
tube and the cathode tube is a very non-linear device.
所以对于输入电压V，屏幕上的亮度，我将称之为L
So for an input voltage V, the brightness on the screen, which I am going to call L
对于亮度，是输入电压的功率。
for luminance, was the power of the input voltage.
事实上，它几乎是一个平方定律，所以就是这样;屏幕上某点的亮度
In fact, it was almost a square law, so that is; the luminance of a point on the screen
大约是输入电压的平方-输入电压升至2.2的功率。
was about the square of the input voltage—the input voltage raised to the power of 2.2.
因此，这个数字2.2被称为显示设备的伽玛。
So this number, 2.2, is referred to as the gamma of the display device.
所以这有点困难。
So this is a bit of a difficulty.
输出亮度与输入电压不成线性比例。
The output luminance is not linearly proportional to the input voltage.
现在让我们为系统添加一个摄像头。
Now let’s add a camera to the system.
因此，相机看着世界，它看到亮度L，并将其转换为电压。
So the camera looks at the world and it sees luminance L and it converts that to a voltage.
电压传输到电视接收器，电视接收器产生
The voltage is transmitted to the television receiver, and the television receiver produces
亮度，与输入电压升高到伽马功率有关。
a luminance, which is related to the input voltage raised to the power of gamma.
现在发生的是我们的系统从头到尾不是线性的。
And what happens now is that our system is not linear from end to end.
我在屏幕上看到的亮度是原始亮度提升到的功率
The luminance that I see on my screen is the original luminance raised to the power of
伽玛，这将对对比度产生非常糟糕的影响。
gamma, and that is going to have a really bad effect on contrast.
如果原始图像的一部分是我在屏幕上的另一部分亮度的两倍
If one part of the original image is twice as bright as another on the screen that I
我看着，它的亮度几乎会增加四倍。
am looking at, it will appear to be almost four times greater in brightness.
因此，为了解决这个问题，早期的电视工程师提出了一个非常巧妙的技巧。
So to get around this problem the early television engineers pulled a pretty neat trick.
他们所做的是将相反的非线性插入相机：亮度
And what they did is they inserted the inverse non-linearity into the camera: the luminance
我在电视屏幕上看到的与电视场景的亮度成正比
that I see on my TV screen is proportional to the luminance of the scene that the TV
相机在看。
camera was looking at.
现在系统从头到尾是线性的。
The system now is linear from end to end.
这对于观看电视图像的人来说非常好。
And that is great for the person viewing the TV image.
因此，相机内的过程称为伽玛编码和之间的图像
So the process within the camera is referred to as gamma encoding and the image between
相机和电视屏幕被称为伽马编码图像。
the camera and the TV screen is referred to as a gamma encoded image.
伽玛解码的过程，或有时称为伽马校正，发生在
And the process of gamma decoding, or sometimes called gamma correction, happens within the
显示屏。
display screen.
现在，这与今天相关的是那些伽马编码的图像是我们记录的
Now where this is relevant today is those gamma encoded images are what we record in
图像文件。
image files.
因此，如果我采用标准图像文件格式，JPEG文件或其他任何像素值
So if I take a standard image file format, a JPEG file or whatever, the pixel values
在该文件中已经过伽马编码。
within that file have been gamma encoded.
它们与相机正在观看的场景的亮度线性不相关。
They are not linearly related to the luminance of the scene that the camera is looking at.
在几乎任何图像文件格式的标题中都有一个条目，其中说：
And in the header of almost any image file format there is an entry there, which says:
什么是相机中使用的伽玛设置。
what’s the gamma setting that has been used in the camera.
即使阴极射线管早已消失，这仍然是方便的原因
The reason that this is still convenient even though cathode ray tubes have long gone is
图像文件中的那些图像像素将显示在屏幕上，
that those image pixels in the image file are going to be displayed on your screen,
正如我之前所说，即使是现代的屏幕也能模仿旧的阴极射线管的非线性。
and as I said before even modern screens emulate the old cathode ray tube non-linearity.
因此，记住图像文件中的像素值是非常重要的
So it is really important to remember that the pixel values within an image file are
与现实世界的亮度没有线性关系。
not linearly related to the real world luminance.
它们与亮度相关，相对于γ的功率为1;事实上，它几乎是
They are related to that luminance to the power of 1 over gamma; in fact, it is almost
平方根函数。
a square root function.
所以我们可以进行伽马校正，我们可以将其视为一元函数。
So we can do gamma correction, we can treat that as a monadic function.
该功能基本上是我们采用每个输入像素并将其提升到伽玛的功率。
The function is basically we take every input pixel and raise it to the power of gamma.
我们可以看到这种映射基本上是抛物线形状。
And we can see that there is basically a parabolic shape to this mapping.
如果我们将它应用于图像并查看它，我们会发现图像看起来非常非常
And if we apply it to an image and look at it, we see that the image looks very, very
确实很黑。
dark indeed.
原因就是我所做的是伽马校正此图像两次。
And the reason for that is that what I have done is gamma corrected this image twice.
我通过应用这个monadic函数，然后我的屏幕，伽马校正图像，
I have gamma corrected the image by applying this monadic function and then my screen,
或者您的屏幕，再次应用了伽马校正。
or your screen, has applied the gamma correction again.
因此，如果您想要查看和操作，则应用伽马校正会很有用
So it can be useful to apply gamma correction if you want to look at and manipulate the
像素值，因为您希望它们与原始光照水平成比例
pixel values, because you want them to be proportional to the original light levels
在场景中，但在显示器上显示伽马校正图像并不是一件有用的事情
in the scene, but to display a gamma corrected image on a monitor is not a useful thing to
做。
do.